Mystery Science Theater 3000, Joe 418, Wario 1.
In the not too distant future, next Sunday A.D.
There was a guy named Joe, not too different from you or me.
He worked at Gizmonic Institute, just another face in a red gel suit.
He did a good job cleaning up the place, but his boss didn't like him so they shot him into space.
We'll send him cheesy movies, the worst we can find.
He'll have to sit and watch them all and the monitor is mine.
Now keep in mind, Joe can't control where the movies begin or end.
Because he used those special parts to make his robot friends.
Robot, cool, cool, camo, fan-lift, gypsy, hi girl, Tom Servo, what a cool guy, cool.
You're wondering how he eats and breathes and other science facts.
Never be to yourself, it's just the show.
I should really just relax for Mystery Science Theater 3000.
(Music)
Hi friend. Hi buddy. You're my best friend. And you're my bestest friend.
Hi everybody, welcome to the satellite of love. I'm just observing my robots, Tom Servo and Kroyz.
They go through their best friend stage. Watch with me.
What do you want to do friend? Oh, I don't know pal, what do you want to do?
Whatever you want to do compadre, we're friends. We certainly are the best of friends.
Why, friends for life. I'd take a bullet for you. Oh and I'd do your jail time. Really?
Say, you want to hit each other real hard and rub our bruises together? No friend.
Oh, you want to shock frogs with a battery charger? No friend.
Oh, you know I'm really not that fond of you. Alright you, you smell bad.
You're dumb. Well you're a jerk. You're adorbous. I got your arm. I got your nose.
I guess they grew out of that stage pretty fast. We'll be right back.
(Music)
Hey, do you like that crow kid? I mean like I used to like him and stuff, but then some other friends of mine are going,
they're going, man is that crow kid ever a lame-o and a jerk. And I'm going, man is that ever true.
Come on Tom, you can't mean that. Joel, he's a dumb smelly dickweed and stuff.
Hey, what you guys talking about? You.
Oh, something nice I presume. Never mind Robin, Laura, Colleen.
Hey, you done with my arm yet?
Well, Joel, as you know, many prominent American woodworkers have, well, died.
Yes, they're dead. Not meant as a criticism, but still true.
Which is the basis of our invention exchange this week. It's the router Ouija board.
Sure, any ordinary Ouija board can contact spirits from beyond the grave.
But with the router Ouija board, when you're in contact with the spirit of a dead woodworker.
Lost in the haury underworld.
You get woodworking done with the pride and craft unknown in the world of the living.
Now, Joel, prepare yourself for we are in contact with someone or something known as Ethan Allen.
Oh, Ethan Allen, most powerful and revered woodworker. Give us a sign.
Wow, I hope they conjure up Homer Formby next.
Homer Formby's not dead.
He isn't? No.
What the heck am I thinking of?
Next week, we will demonstrate the lathe of heaven.
Why don't you go ahead with your invention exchange, Joel?
Sure, remember this old gag? Thanks for holding, crow.
Oh, hi, Joel. Hey, how's hobby? Hey, put Dory on, would you?
Ow, crow.
Yes, the squirting phone. A classic on the level of the spitting clam.
Now it's been updated and digitized for the 90s. Say hello to the funny gag facts.
You just feed the paper in like any fax machine, add a little water, and fire away at some unsuspecting rooba 100 miles away.
You set up down there, sirs?
Ah, Frank, there's a fax coming through this. Now, you see, I told you this would start paying for itself as soon as we plugged it in.
(Grunting)
It's for you. Oh, thank you. Hmm.
Hmm. Interesting. Interesting. Here, check this out.
Really? What is it?
Take a look here.
(Grunting)
Just for that, Joel, I'm going to send you attack of the eye creatures. Which I was going to do anyway. Push the button, Frank.
That's okay, you'll get them next time. You'll be okay.
Would you put that thing down?
God!
Oh, we got one side!
(Cheering)
Whoa. You okay, Cro?
Yeah, I love that joke.
The untouchables.
The defiant temps.
Hey, he got arrested by a ventriloquial figure.
It was a dull movie and Allstate was there.
Well, time to end my film premiere? No.
I know, I know. I look like the Bulldog and the Warner Brothers cartoon.
Hey, nice area. I think.
Okay, it's a four dollar cover. Good luck in there, if you know what I mean. Go get 'em, tiger.
Come in.
Welcome to the third grade.
May I see your credentials?
Certainly.
Jeez, he's getting carded.
Picture came in.
You ought to have a key.
Yes, it arrived by special messenger late this afternoon.
I'll just, uh... Damn, I hate these things.
Would you just get it open, please?
Sorry.
Boy, lunch is really a big deal around here.
Good morning, Mr. Phelps.
Hey, I said show your work.
B minus. Work on your penmanship.
Please excuse Johnny from gym class. He's a top secret agent.
Here's your receipt.
That's for tax purposes.
I don't need to remind you of the necessity for absolute security on this general.
No!
Jeez.
I realize that civilization itself may depend on it. Good luck.
I resent him, uh...
Oh, what was I doing? Oh.
Oh, yeah.
Sergeant, send that Lieutenant Robertson from Security Sector 3 in here.
And put the Azalea Pictures Presents up.
All right, boys to the gym, please. Girls to the home ec room.
If AV geeks rule the world...
We do.
Attack of the the eye creatures did Mel Tillis write these titles or what?
God, we'll be starting the movie in a second. Please be patient, people.
Like, what, these brackets?
There's some leader.
Uh, Sinbad, I'm not sure.
Let's bracket some leader. Uh, Cynthia Hull?
Here.
Warren Hammock?
Yo! Chet Davis?
Present. Bill Peck?
Not here.
Very funny, Mr. Peck.
The Dockers commercial.
Ethan Allen? Wow, he must be old.
Uh, Tony Houston, we have a problem.
Jonathan Ledford Seagull?
What time is the pistol whipping?
Some hall monitor, huh?
Eh, you a commie? Just checking.
Well, go in. What are you waiting for?
Coming.
Pink young house boy reporting for duty, sir.
Lieutenant Robertson reporting as ordered.
Sit down, Lieutenant. Relax.
So, tell me, why do you want to be a prep cook at Denny's?
So, are you responsible for the triple whip out in the cafeteria?
As you know, Robertson, your Sector 3 has not been cleared for receipt of materials on project visitors.
I know! Tell Robertson!
I'd like to give you a verbal briefing for relay to Colonel Harrison.
I ask that you not take notes, but that you absorb everything you see and hear.
I'm your sponge, sir.
...certain events which I'm not at liberty to disclose.
We feel that Sector 3 will be the probable place for the next contact.
I'll get the snacks. You like combos?
Now, pay close attention to the information recorded on this film.
It was prepared by elves section of our UFO division.
Prepared by elves? What, in a hollow tree?
This latest military film concerning project visitors was obtained from the remote controlled high altitude satellite space eyes.
As well as from ground tracking stations.
I'm Peter Graves or Amy Lager.
The alien ship sighted was of a completely unfamiliar design and came under hyper radar and infrared surveillance at 2300 hours yesterday.
The alien ship veered for a close pass at the United States remote meteorological laboratory in orbit 15CX.
It came with ham and a choice of font.
Communication was made. The orbiting object then resumed its Earth intercept course at a rocky point along the Sierra Madre in the western portion of the United States.
No, seriously, let's see the real film.
...to the east at an extremely low rate of speed.
Oh yeah, but it...
The official evaluation of headquarters command is that the space vehicle is probably manned.
I know, but...
...will affect the surface landing and must be presumed to be unfriendly.
Well, sure, but...
It is imperative that absolutely no public information be released at this time to prevent the probable worldwide panic.
From a bagel witch?
...lost contact with the vehicle over the central United States in the general area of security sector 6.
Should you or any of your I.M. force be caught or killed, the secretary will disavow any knowledge of your action.
Any questions?
Yeah, what the heck was that about?
I'm in here.
Alright, lieutenant, your transportation's waiting. You should be back in your sector within an hour.
Oh, lieutenant...
Nice pants.
You tell Colonel Harrison that I want those infrared scanners manned every minute, 24 hours a day, and that's an order.
Yes, sir.
Take off.
To the great white north.
Bed spring world at the Landonod mattress factory.
Got anything on the infrared scope?
Yep. Moving body.
Sandy Baron and Robert Wohl are back.
Get out of the scanner.
And now, the most instantly unappealing character in film history.
Oh, you know, Pontiacs are really funny if you look at them in the right way.
Forty-nine dollars, Dan. Forty-nine dollars a month driving away.
Better deal with this again.
Ain't science wonderful? I only found out about it after I got in the Air Force.
He's Charles Nelson Riley's understudy.
Go to close.
Yes, sir, sergeant.
Oh, it's the All Kennedy Channel.
All Kennedy.
Harold?
Yeah?
Harold, somehow I had the feeling that...
Well, that Gaussian equations are flawed due to their strict Euclidean view of the universe.
Here we are, Bill. The kids in the other cart.
Later on, we may watch the improv while.
I borrowed a camcorder from Rob Lowe.
But Harold, I just know they're watching us.
Good. Now that's over.
Come on, let me ram my nose into your ear.
The feeling I have is like...
It's like someone out there is watching us.
It's just your imagination, pussycat.
There's no one here but us chickens.
Oh, I truly admire science.
Oh, wise guy, eh?
All right, sergeant. What's up?
I am, sir.
Nothing, sir.
Just testing the infrared equipment.
That means you're playing Pee-pee Tom again, right?
Right, sir.
Colburn, how many times have you been busted for pulling shenanigans just like that?
You mean this year, sir?
All together.
(Singing)
Three times, sir.
We're here for a reason.
We got booted out of our way.
A reason important to the national security, and don't ever forget it.
No, sir.
Don't!
We're here to watch the skies and not the skylines, right?
Right, sir.
You're ever so right, sir.
Bad things are going on up there, right?
How bad things are going on right in this room, I think.
What kind of things, sir?
Never you mind.
You're here to watch the sky and not the skylines.
Again with a finger.
Right? Oh, boy, are you ever right, sir?
Right, sir.
Now that that's established, let's take a look and see how the infra scanner's working.
And now, Red in the silent spot.
Red's a perverted serviceman with lots of time.
Geez, Henry Portrait of a Serial Killer is not as sick as this.
Oh, Harold.
Oh, Maude. Maude.
Yeah, how about that?
This is sick.
Sir.
Well, they get Charlie Chaplin to write the music.
And now the little fellow makes out.
Hey, hey, hey, Harold, my hero.
Joel, I need a shower.
Well, back to business, ma'am.
It's Larry, Daryl, and Daryl.
I always get the little girl up when I get into town.
How will you find her?
I'd recognize her eyes.
Any place.
Oh, I refuse to watch this.
The place most of these kids end up is the pokey.
Of course not.
They're good kids.
They end up at the terrace at the lake.
Not that I go to places like that.
Not that I would have a healthy relationship.
But I've heard of whatever the lieutenant says, sir.
I'm with him, sir.
The White Rock Cafe where Whitey comes to drink and dance.
Wonderful, wonderful. Thank you, boys.
Rock and roll can lead to meeting other people with similar interests.
Yeah.
Brought to you by White Beer.
There's a trailer park of flavor in every bottle.
Ah, will there be anything else?
Right now I can't afford what I'm thinking.
Oh, shut up. Not you now.
I got news for you. You never will.
Say, there is one thing.
I was wondering if you could tell me how to...
What's this word in the state's directions? Emotes?
I have written on writing gear. Let's see.
Could you tell me how to get to...
Polly Holiday's house?
First base with you tonight?
I'd like to apologize for the entire mail tender now.
At least I tried.
Thanks. I'm sorry.
Trying's all we ever do ever since we hit this town.
We should have never come here in the first place.
Guess a guy's got to be a native in this bird before a dam will give him a break.
No, give me that.
Let's go home. I'm bushed.
I'm quail.
Let's move slow here.
I got a tip that this town's a cinch for a quick buck.
A whole dollar?
All we have to do is get some kind of pitch going at the fairground.
Now's all we have to worry about finding the right thing.
Skip it. I'm going to bed.
We'll pull out in the morning.
I'm loaded for action tonight.
I'll take a drive and see what I can pick up.
Bad chance.
Remember, the car's half mine, so drive carefully.
You're half the front seat.
You won't be using your half-munch tonight.
Wet head and dry look.
Oh, mouth, no action.
Ew.
No, I want to walk off my great expectations.
The wheels of progress.
Or should I say the progress of a big wheel?
I resent that.
I can't believe I made those two guys.
The onion field.
I don't know about you guys, but I'm rooting for the eye creatures.
Hey, dim your cuff links.
Chip Douglas, you come in here this instant.
It's a cow sill.
Oh, well, it's the end of the world as we know it. I feel fine.
How about that, baby?
Oh, Harold, when you kiss me...
Turn it off! Turn it off!
I just see explosions.
You know what? When he kisses her, I see explosions...
You know what? You are one sick mama-jama.
Looks like he walked right out of a J. Crew catalog.
(Siren wails)
# I'm never gonna give you up
# Never gonna let you down
# Never gonna fall... #
Oh, so bright.
Heh, heh, heh.
He looks like Roy Cohn.
Hammer.
Huh, Mariah Carey's running through the woods.
OK, I can go now.
You sure it was out by the old Bailey house?
Sure, dead sure.
It was probably a plane going down.
Anything could happen when these crazy electrical storms were around.
That's it. Low lightning. What else?
How dare you negate me?
You still believe the old Bailey house is haunted?
Maybe the ghosts have come back.
That old place was built before the Civil War.
Could be.
Well, how's your recruiting coming along, Lieutenant?
Not bad.
Why don't you, uh, Shanghai a couple of them?
Are you kidding?
Wonder what they've jabbering about.
Oh, art, science, critical theory, you know.
She dresses like a bobber.
I don't see any girls around, so what's keeping you Romeos so busy?
Jim just saw a spaceship.
Only one?
With all the beer he drank, you'd think he'd see at least six.
(Laughs)
Drink this one.
I like gum.
I've heard the yellow ones myself.
Hey, speaking of, uh, yellow ones...
How's your tea?
Why don't you all go over and talk to that Air Force recruiting officer?
Yeah, he makes improper advances.
So that's what he is.
I've seen him hanging around, too.
That's what he says he is.
This place has all the ambiance of a Vietnamese restaurant.
Well, the boys were just kidding about seeing a spaceship, Lieutenant.
Everyone knows there's no such thing.
How many times do we have to deny it before people will believe us?
Well, excuse me, fly boy.
Oh, I'll get back to you when I think of an insult.
Better watch out.
The way things are going, he may be giving some of you orders next month.
Man, I'm hooked.
They're dragging me in feet first.
Don't you have a date with Susan tonight?
I do. I'm picking her up at 9.30.
She's, uh, fussing with a new dress.
You can take her with us.
We know you're waiting for her old man to get out of the house.
What kind of dress takes that long to get into?
Waitress, I think we're done.
Susan's got a lot of the right things to put in the right places.
Yeah.
And they're all mine.
Ooh!
Right, we'll see.
I admire him.
We now return to Macon County line.
Do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do.
Go and get me a piece of bottom land.
Jesse Helms in retirement.
Yay! Kill all the characters! Woo!
Another carload of them blasted smooches on my property.
I'll get the law after 'em.
Thank you for providing a running commentary.
I can't seem to get the stink out.
The wind song stays in my car.
Look, little Billy left his toy on the lawn.
There's a twig in front of him.
Run! There's a snap-tight bottle in the woods.
What are you, Jamie Lee Curtis?
Little red shev that.
Ron Howard pops the clutch and tells the world to eat his dust.
Boy, sure is dark tonight, huh?
Ooh, dark.
Look, people have a right to drive on the road, old man. Come on.
I'll fix 'em.
And I'm let to maybe continental breakfast, but that's it.
They ain't gonna work on Maggie's farm no more.
Tiger!
Darling, your head is full.
Tonight as usual.
Why not? We're only young ones.
Besides, I'm gonna show you the moon.
God, no, please, stay seated.
I can see you anytime.
You can.
Yes.
Ooh, she's got a praying mantis.
All right, go get 'em, Tiger.
Huh.
Hey, whoa. Take it easy.
Not so fast. I'm out of breath.
Calling Susan Faludi. Calling Susan Faludi.
I'm eloping with you tonight.
That's proof enough, isn't it?
It sure is, seeing how your father hates me.
Don't get a fool that bad.
(engine starts)
Whoa, Tommy, that is one sweet ride.
Well, hop in.
Oh, yeah, no thanks. Your driving makes me scared.
Oh, we won't drive anywhere.
I thought we could be like the teeners in the movie.
You know, sit and talk for a while, then maybe make out.
Oh, okay, that sounds like fun. What?
Make out. You know, smooch, like in the movie.
Okay, now let's figure this out.
First you scooch over close to me, then tilt your head back and moan.
Oh, my God, no!
Ah!
Huh, wonder what's eating him.
Hi, Tom.
Hi.
Hey, sweet ride.
Thanks. Hey, you want to make out?
(laughs)
Oh, come on, please, as a friend, I've never been kissed before, except on my arm,
and I've never tasted lips.
Commercial sign in two minutes.
Say, magic voice.
No, Tom, I won't.
Well, actually, I can't. I have no physical form.
But you do know about it.
Making out? Sure, it's nothing new.
Well, I guess I've heard of it before, too.
It just never struck me like it did today.
It seemed brand new.
And, well, I have so many questions, like, why?
Why does one make out?
And once you've started, how do you know when you're done?
Now, I consider it a greeting, like a firm handshake, only with the lips.
Am I right?
Oh, yeah, and is it necessary to use the lips?
I mean, could I kiss with my forehead or my elbow?
And are the teeth involved?
And where the heck do you store your tongue?
Another thing, be a sucker blow.
Is it under some sort of strict rabbinical supervision or something?
And here's a puzzler, who kisses whom and when?
I mean, being a robot, can I kiss animals?
Or am I confined to a single species?
Oh, yeah, I can't pucker. Is that a handicap?
How can a man in a single lifetime know everything there is to know about making out?
You know something, mister? You ask too many questions.
Well, I'm only complaining--
Mwah!
You know, I've always wanted to do that.
Hmm.
I'm sorry, Tom. I was just teasing.
Oh.
Mike, we've made it.
What a surprise. He lives in a shabby furnace room.
Travis, Bickel had a better room than this.
Wake up, I said. Mike, we've got it made. We're millionaires.
Really? I thought we were oily drifters.
But this is different. It's big.
Now, look, I'm not trying to give you a pitch, but get this.
Term insurance.
You and me are going to put on an exhibition--
No!
--first and only, truly authentic spaceship.
You woke me up to tell me that?
Told you it was big, didn't I?
Well, I've seen one.
Just like all these jokers have been saying.
It's big and round and glows sort of funny-like.
Oh, that's the big boy sign.
And gets on this funny sound like--
[growling]
That's great.
Police! Police!
Like that, huh?
Yeah.
And it landed over somewhere near that old house that's supposed to be haunted.
Great, isn't it?
Not what you want.
All right, get in.
I forgot to ask you, how was your day?
It's punchin' goofy.
All right.
But when I'm rolling in the dough, don't say that I didn't invite you in.
Okay.
You're invited out.
I'll handle it myself.
Stanley, get me a hammer.
Go back to sleep.
Sleep your life away.
Now pick me up some pomade while you're out.
Oh.
Looks like the cover of Bed, or Homes and Gardens.
Pyle, get in here!
Honey, what happened to your hair?
Why, these blasted alarms always at night.
Phil Silvers.
About this so-called spaceship of yours.
Richard Deacon.
From what these kids said, it must be somewhere northeast of town.
Well, that checks for the last report we had from the radar station.
I assume your man had it on the scope.
And we better get right out there, sir.
The general was pretty sore at us for letting the last one get out of our scope.
Army intelligence really scooped us that time.
Scoop, did you say?
Joker Abiola.
Just a figure of speech, sir.
Well, I hope so.
Wally Shawn.
There's just one thing I want to caution you about.
Toe-fool.
In civilian life, you were a publicity man.
I was a leopard boy on the circus.
Just this.
Our job is to prevent a possible nationwide panic by keeping the information from the public.
Fred Clark.
I figured a public information officer is about the last thing we need.
I didn't request this assignment, sir.
I know that.
But get this straight, Robertson.
If you leave one word of any of this to your cronies, I'll have you court-martialed and shocked.
Do I make myself clear?
Uh, what was the middle part again?
Indeed, sir.
Good.
Now go down the hall and get your men.
And tell them to load their weapons.
Bill Silver's Richard Dicken, Jackie Leonard, Joe Brantiello, Wally Shawn, Fred Clark, ladies and gentlemen.
Dear Abby, I'm an elderly woman who doesn't...
Smoochers!
Oh, that was just the house settling, I hope.
We now join Ernest Hemingway at his home in Ketchum, Idaho.
A toe in there.
Hey, granny, kids, I'll get them yet.
Can hardly see the road.
We want to get there in one piece.
Relax, honey, it's only about a half a mile to the highway.
We'll make it.
Nothing to be afraid of.
Man, it's really hard to see the road when it's noon.
You know, Joe, maybe your head's like an egg sack, or maybe it's for water storage, or...
Stop ahead!
I will if I see one rolling by.
Leader of the pack.
I don't know, it happened so fast.
I didn't even see it.
Hey, wait for me.
Last one to the plot points, a rotten egg.
Stan, what have we done?
It's a body we've...
Come on, give me a hand, let's take him to the hospital.
Beluga caviar.
He ran over a fungus.
Dad.
I think we killed the Michelin Man.
Is it still alive?
Whatever it is, I killed him.
It's dead, Jim.
I think I'm going to be sick.
Come here.
Stan, take me away from here.
Calgon, take me away.
Hand jive, hand jive, doing the hand jive.
Tika, tika, tika, tika, tika.
You're soaking in it.
The meds are gross.
What was that?
Oh, sorry, that's me.
It's a tire.
The fender must have cut it when we hit that thing.
Are we stuck here?
Well, we can't drive on it.
We're right off the rim and I haven't got a spare.
So, let's make out.
Let's go to the old bailing house and call the police.
That's all we can do.
I'll be back.
What was that?
I don't know, space alien, bloody hand.
Wind, I guess.
Come on.
We now return to the eyes of Laura Mars.
Boy, it is dark.
I just wanted to find our way.
Sessions presents John Denver.
Central Roads, take me home.
Oh, let's go to the Tobe Hooper place.
Egan.
Nice place.
Let's try the last house on the left here.
Andy?
Opie?
Floyd?
Buddy?
Hi, honey, we're doomed.
Can we leave you a watchtower?
I'll just stay on the steps while you get murdered.
What's the matter?
Well, the kids, they say this place is haunted.
And they say that falling in love is wonderful.
They got a feeling that whatever's in there,
this is a lot safer than what's out here.
Hyman, someone's at the door.
Anybody home?
Well, it looks like the Hooterville Hotel.
Hurry, Stan, we've got no right to be here.
I wonder where he keeps his phone.
I wonder if he has a phone.
Oh, ma'am, that is cold.
Is he a dream or a dog?
What?
February, June and May.
I'd rather do it myself.
I'd rather you did it too.
Opening strange doors isn't the thing
for a good, clean, living American girl to do.
You're right.
You can never tell what's on the other side.
What kind of a declaration is that?
Who wrote that dialogue?
Hey, Stan, there's the phone on the wall.
Oh, thanks.
Now, you see, there's nothing to be afraid of.
You just keep your wits about you
and things begin to take on the proper--
Dr. Trebes, would you like to see my cathedral?
It's weighted.
Very lucky girl to have a guy like me.
Keep telling me.
The old guy is very well read.
Oh, John Gacy makeup book, the Speck Whitman letters.
Give me the police department.
It's an emergency.
Kind of an easygoing emergency, but still.
Eddie Haskell.
Like it's ever for me.
Yep.
Hello?
My name is Kenyon, Stan Kenyon.
Stan Kenyon, wow.
Yeah, yeah, go on then.
The upper corner locker.
Yeah.
Yeah, there we go.
Yeah, my sport court's wrinkled.
Oh, sure, you've seen some little spacemen.
Don't look at me.
That's better.
I know, from another planet.
10-speed brown shoe.
Look, do me a favor.
If you see him again, will you give him my love
and tell him to go home?
God, I hate the public.
Well, it's Saturday night, all right.
Lithium cups.
That just made it official.
That's it, hit him with a People's Choice Award.
You got a passum under your head, girly?
What are you doing in my house?
You're right, he does look like a spaceman.
Hi, Mr. Bailey, we hit something with our car
and we came up here to call the police.
You were out.
The door was open.
That don't give you a right to walk in.
Who was it you hit?
It wasn't a person, it was a thing.
Oh, it don't make no difference.
It all spells people.
You're a communist.
And people spells trouble.
I knew it.
I didn't know what was gonna happen
if you kids didn't stay off my property.
Suffering sack of tats.
Yeah.
We'll call the police, all right.
The phone's dead.
That's what you say.
Ed Asner, in a role that will surprise you.
Look, we didn't kill anybody.
I mean, it wasn't a person.
It was a space thing, a monster.
I know it sounds crazy.
But I'm Punky Brewster.
You kids been drinking?
No.
Yes.
No, sir.
What's your name, Sonny?
Stan Kenyon.
Stan Kenyon?
Wow.
Yeah, I thought I'd seen you before.
We didn't hurt anything human.
I took...
Okay, we'll go.
And you tell your friends
they'd better keep off of my property.
Or they'll get a backside full of rock salt.
Yes, sir.
Now you get...
Backside full of rock salt, yes, sir.
All right, come on, get!
Okay.
Wait, come back.
I don't know how to love.
I miss you already.
James A. Michener's Adventures in...
Okay, put me through to Dub Taylor,
Will Gear, and Struther Mountain.
Hello, Sarah?
Tell them to send some cops out here
and chase these smooches off of my property.
What are you wearing, Sarah?
All right.
Yeah.
See that you do.
I'm not a police officer myself,
but if you'd like to stable...
Midsection Playhouse presents...
A fun couple.
Too bad they're gonna die.
It sure is dark out there.
I hope they don't get a moon burn.
Still trying to hear that wind song out of my car.
She's gonna have fun, fun, fun till her daddy takes that away.
Ow.
Bumps when you cook it.
Okay, Jed, let's take it from the top.
Okay, so I exit from my house wielding my gun.
What's my motivation?
Your paycheck.
Smockers. It has to taste good.
Chips. That's what I mean.
A Quinn Martin production.
He's wearing hammer pants. Check it out.
I wonder what made him so cranky.
Oh, well, he's in group therapy with Pa Joe, Grandpa Walton.
He's a good guy.
Oh, well, he's in group therapy with Pa Joe, Grandpa Walton, Ma and Pa Kettle.
I heard my bouncing Betty go off.
Oh, I hate smooch.
Oh, that's not me. I'm the young guy.
There.
Check it out.
Can I get a pillow, please?
On emergency 911, an eye creature is down.
Rough boys under the street.
You don't want to bark?
Night falls. Sort of.
The driving scene will haunt your dreams.
Wow, it's really dark here.
Boy, oh, boy.
Hey, it's John boy back from college.
I'm selling subscriptions to Smootcher magazine.
Anybody home?
You audience members, you've been smooching, haven't you?
Teenage wasteland.
They're all wasted.
You worms and bugs, you've been smooching down there?
Mike, Carl.
Steve, Earl, Ed, Link, Julie, Scott.
Listen, Mike.
This time I've got proof.
What is it, Carl?
I've got bed sores.
Listen, Mike.
I can't tell you what it is, but I swear I'm telling you the truth.
I can't tell you what it is.
There was another gunman behind the fence.
Because I don't know what it is.
It's stuck under a car.
Now listen, Mike.
Get a cab and come out here.
I need your help.
Yeah, well, that's too bad.
I'm going back to sleep.
But Mike.
But I'm not going to sleep.
Mike.
But nothing.
Goodbye.
Mike, don't hang up.
Now listen, do me just one favor.
Faith.
Clean everything out of the refrigerator.
The refrigerator?
It's your turn.
Yeah, what I'm bringing home is perishable.
We've got to keep it on ice.
Got it, Mike?
Including the shells.
That's my boy.
You won't regret it.
I swear to you.
You do believe me, don't you?
I'll be right home with it.
Sure.
Everything out of the refrigerator.
Everything.
Got it?
I got it.
Everything you ever wanted out of a refrigerator.
Oh, you are wrong, pomade breasts.
Oh, God.
Ew.
And now red in the silent spot.
Red sports a sweater dress and...
Let's see, buttermilk from last Christmas.
Eggnog from last Christmas.
Fur.
Oh, cat food.
Oh, you schmoocher.
Oh, a single schmoocher.
The worst kind.
(singing)
Beer.
Booze and beer.
Cold beer wine.
DJ swine.
Now, get in and close the door.
What the heck am I doing?
I'm a psycho.
As crazy as he is.
Now the dogs can't control me.
Can you imagine how dingy and yellow his sheets are?
Ignatius P. Reilly had better hygiene than this guy.
All right, you dig the flipping hall.
We gotta take care of that problem upstate.
Sorry, turns out I'm going camping and I need that blanket.
All right, come on.
Come on, eye creature.
I'm gonna catch you, man.
I'm gonna catch you.
Ironically, I'm having a hard time seeing.
Zips.
Thank you, thank you.
Fiddle faddle.
Come here, I love you, you big galoot.
Being attacked by creamy nougat centers.
Well, we think you're a bad person and we don't approve of you or your kind and a lot of other bad stuff.
Oh, shiatsu.
It's really good for you.
Well, it's kind of like the present.
It's kind of like the present, huh?
Hey, you guys wanna jump in here and help me?
I'm the only one terrifying him.
There was Forbidden Planet.
Then?
There was Police Woman.
And of course, who can ever forget some of the other movies that he did.
Right.
These are just a few of the many reasons to celebrate Earl Holloman.
Earl Hollomania.
Yes, Earl Hollomania.
As Earl Holloman prepares to undertake the most demanding role of his career,
co-starring with Delta Burke in a new situation comedy, Delta,
well, what better time to salute Earl Holloman?
Earl Holloman.
Earl Holloman, considered by many to be the poor man's Martin Milner.
Yes, beloved Earl Holloman.
Earl Holloman, whose promising film career really didn't work out that good.
Earl Holloman.
Earl Holloman, who embraced the role of Sergeant Bill Crowley
and flourished on the television drama, Police Woman Earl Holloman.
Earl Holloman, whose immortal words, "Pepper, you're going undercover,"
became the anthem of a disenfranchised generation who, until that moment,
had nothing to believe in but their own unwe'en.
Earl Holloman, who may very well have, in all likelihood,
all evidence points to him having been,
was probably a guest star in Lancer at one time.
And indisputably, one of the major forces in '70s television was Aaron Spelling.
Earl Holloman, who seems like he should have had a part in the Big Valley,
but will always be remembered for Police Woman.
Because who can forget Earl Holloman's groundbreaking role in Police Woman?
Earl Holloman, whose legacy of averageness infused many a movie.
Why, even Attack of the Eye Creatures, in which a certain character,
when filmed at just the right angles, vaguely resembles Earl Holloman.
Just another nod to Earl Holloman!
Earl Holloman, whose enduring friendship with Monty Markham
is chronicled in the bestseller Soulmates, published prepostumously.
To review, Earl Holloman will be forever remembered for his timeless work in Police Woman.
Earl Holloman, who was undeniably, unquestionably in Police Woman,
and you can't take that away from him, dog-gun it.
Earl Holloman, who would have been William Shatner had there not already been one.
Watch for Earl Hollomedia coming to your town soon.
Oh, we got movies now! Let's do this!
Earl Holloman!
But I don't think I believe him.
Hey, Mel Torme wants his do-lap back.
That's the green light our jet pilots have been telling us they've seen.
Now you're cooking with gas.
Sir, enough with the jokes, Lieutenant.
It was more of a quip, sir.
Things turn out to be unfriendly.
You've got a point there, sir.
Shall I drive closer so we can get a better look?
No, let's stay right here. Something may be watching us right now.
We better start smooching.
Airman, get me Guard Headquarters on that shortwave radio.
I'm going to get some engineers right out here and see if we can get inside those things.
You think we should get some photographers, sir?
Some wagons, some roads, some reason maps.
As long as I have, you'll learn you don't have to think.
All you do is follow standard operating procedures.
Ouch.
In this case, SOP calls for engineers, not photographers.
Unless it's Maple Park.
I've got the National Guard.
Give me that thing.
Give me that thing! Give me that thing!
Give me that thing!
Sessions presents Leo Sayer.
When I need love.
Neil Sudecker.
There was a time when strangers were welcome here.
And many more.
It's kind of Miller's Crossing time.
What is it?
It's one of those space things, alive.
What's making that noise?
He's banging away at the theater. I was so kind of a hammer.
I'm on it.
Let's get out of here.
I'm with you.
Sing whenever I sing, whenever I sing, whenever I sing.
Oh, there's a man he's splendid.
You okay?
Yeah.
When do we start a low thing?
How much further?
Just about another quarter of a mile to the highway.
Oh, I wish we had stuck to the main road.
These shoes weren't meant for Plowed Fields.
They were made for walking.
Okay?
My life? Your life?
Well, now, Angie, I gotta take Elvin and Lou up to Mount Pilate.
He's gone.
They must have believed you after all.
Come on, let's go back there. The police will take care of those things.
Whoa! I get out of here.
Thus began their legal nightmare.
O'Neill ambulances. You plug 'em, we lug 'em.
Wait a minute. That's no ambulance. It's a country squire.
Hey, look, they're gonna take their prom picture.
Hey, I want a copy of that.
Okay, now, let's have this again.
You say you were driving along...
Singing a song.
...with your lights.
Yes, sir, but that didn't have anything to do with it.
So he just suddenly appeared.
Suddenly appeared.
From out of the dark.
I'm glad you guys came along.
Yeah, I'll bet you are.
Doc, over here.
This is my puppet, Peppy.
Kids, before I take you down to headquarters, I want you to do something for me, okay?
I'm a high-energy prop cop.
See this nice little balloon?
Well, I want you to blow it up.
Balloon?
What for? We gonna have a party?
Never mind. Just blow.
Hey, come on, look, we're wasting time now.
Aren't you gonna do anything about the spaceman?
It may be a whole invasion.
Blow, I said!
Boy, kind of a jerk for a cop.
Man says blowy means it.
When in Rome...
Yes, I worked for Benny Hill for many years.
Did you ever hear such a cock and bull story?
Space men, space ships.
William Burroughs is a young man.
In my days, we were content with pink elephants, but kids these days.
And tough, the gal says to me, "You don't call him human, do you?"
What do you think about that?
Well, what can you expect with all these bad books being written nowadays?
Great Gatsby, Ulysses.
I'm finished. Now can we get going or shall I throw a little confetti around?
Here, make a dog out of that.
You know, fella, for someone who's committed a serious crime,
you are very anxious to get to the police station.
A serious crime?
You call killing one of those monsters a crime?
The script is a crime.
Something's weird around here.
Something is wrong on Saturn 3.
Something or somebody. Come on, let's go.
Hey, do you think it would be alright if maybe my girlfriend got arrested too or something?
Old Blue Eyes is back.
The summer wind came blowing in across that cuckoo sea.
Now you'll just read this before you sign it.
Look, this is silly. We told you what happened. Now why don't you do something?
That's exactly what we're doing, Miss.
Just ram-riding you through the legal system.
It's not a statement. It's a confession.
It's typing.
Now look, you admit driving the car, don't you?
I told you that.
And with the lights off?
Right, but that doesn't...
Now look, buddy boy, whether you realize it or not,
driving without your lights and killing the man is against the law in this state.
Killing a man? For snoring too loud?
You can call that thing a man, do you?
And I haven't even added in drunk driving yet, but when we get the balloons...
Julie Nixon.
That's another strike against you.
Look, officer, my father's city attorney and I demand that you send for him right away.
Oh, everyone wants their rights.
Well, Miss, it so happens that I know your father and he's already been sent for you.
He'll straighten you out all right.
Look, uh...
I don't want the siding.
Now you want to try to beat it out of me, you go ahead.
No, really, I insist. Beat it out of me.
Never fail. Try to be nice to a young punk and next thing you know,
you're up on charges of using the third degree.
What's this about the third degree?
Uh, closer to the mic.
Hi, who are you?
Oh, Daddy, these people are crazy.
Their prices are so low.
Dan and I have had a horrible time.
It's a villa.
Thought you told me you were going out with Bill Moore, not with this roughneck.
But don't you want to hear about the monster?
No.
You heard that ridiculous story when the sergeant called.
Now listen to me, sir.
If it's humanly possible, I'll get you out of this mess.
First we deflate your hair.
He can take his medicine.
But he can't dish it out.
Is this where the beating is?
We'll be right over.
If you'll come with me, we'll make the formal identification.
Have I ever worn a formal?
Look, Mr. Rogers, wait until you see this thing and then maybe you'll believe it.
Oh, no more close-ups, please.
Eat. Eat. Eat. Eat.
I'm reporting now from Grover's Mill, New Jersey.
Go ahead.
We have you surrounded.
Come out and you will not be harmed.
Come out with your eyes up.
I don't believe anybody's in that thing.
Probably under remote control.
Would you like to take a walk out there in the open and test your theory?
Why, yes, darling, if you'll accompany me.
No, sir, not especially.
Then shut up and start thinking of a way to explain this thing without throwing the whole nation into a complete panic.
I hope your heart blows up, sir.
Yes, sir.
Beg your pardon, sir.
Maybe if we fire a few rounds at it, we'd scare someone out.
Shut up.
Who the heck are you?
All right.
Go ahead.
Yes, sir.
It's a Simon game.
Getting nowhere.
Come on down to O'Neill Funeral Chapel.
Over 10,000 ossified customers.
Man, they've got a really good buffet in here.
So are the eye creatures there for the visitation?
Oh, my gosh, an old boat.
The worst kind.
Table for two.
The unspoken language of bald men.
What the heck did you say to him?
Oh, very nice.
Hope you like him.
I did the frosting myself.
Well, dig in.
He's perfect.
I love him.
Well, I didn't run over this man.
I ran over a monster.
Are you still on that kick?
You see, Mr. Rogers, I didn't exaggerate.
Look, Mr. Rogers, sir, I swear, I'm telling the truth.
It was a spaceman.
I've heard enough of that.
I saw it with my own hair.
You know who he is?
Well, according to a driver's license we found on him,
his name is Carl Hinton.
Sagan.
We also found out he lives at 121 Maple Avenue.
How does he work?
As far as we can discover, he doesn't.
Actor, huh?
He and a friend of his kind of just drifted into town
about a month ago.
Oh, they're the drifters.
Yeah, a fella he was talking with.
Ah, gotcha.
We tried to call him to come down and identify the body,
but he, well, we didn't get an answer.
You're uglier than I am.
Say, can I talk to them alone for a moment?
Where'd that come from?
You mean here, sir?
That's your office.
All right.
Well, that'd actually be pretty neat.
Sorry, we just couldn't wait until we got to the office,
could you?
Are we under arrest?
Do we have the right to remain silent?
And if we give up that right, do we, uh--
Guy walks into a bar.
In one respect, the man you killed is a nobody.
Okay, then.
There's only one person who's interested in the charges
against you, and that's his roommate.
Cynthia.
Daddy, I swear to you, Stan didn't kill anything.
Quiet, Susan.
At least Stan has the sense to listen.
Now, tomorrow I'll go over and talk to this call friend's roommate.
She's gonna blow.
Come on, Susan, I'm taking you home.
I won't go unless Stan goes.
Don't be foolish.
You're not liable.
Yes, I am.
Well, no, I'm not.
Stan's lying.
He's lying to his big, fat teeth.
I was driving that car.
Hey, now, wait a minute.
What is this, bonfire of the vanities all of a sudden?
It's night, ladies and gentlemen.
Night.
Here, give me that, sergeant.
I'm gonna do my Rudy Valley.
(clears throat)
♪ I'm just a vagabond lover ♪
We've got a deadline to make.
We've almost got it.
Come on, we got a whole movie to shoot by 4.30.
Let's snap it up.
What the?
They're welding back at me.
Hey, look at that.
I hit the bad thing again.
Sounds like someone picked up a spare.
What the?
There's a great disturbance in the force.
Looks like a vincedron explosion over there in the bathing place.
Bye, put an egg in the microwave.
What was that?
Something blew up.
Looks like it's just you and me, Trent.
Easily distracted cops.
I'll work the counter.
Who's supposed to pose that one?
Well, she's new.
I don't care less.
New temps.
Give us something, those things, whatever they are.
They're smarter than all of us put together.
What do you mean?
Remember when we saw them banging away at the fender of our car?
What's so smart about that?
Don't you see?
They killed that man.
And then they dented the fender of my car to make it look like we did it.
It's frame up.
And we thought they were mad at the car.
Right.
So the car is smarter than us?
No, honey, somehow we've got to go back out there and get something,
some kind of evidence that they'll believe because if we don't,
I'm going to jail.
But how they won't let us.
I know it.
Let's see, I wonder where that door is.
Door.
Oh, door.
There it is.
Oh, look at this.
Honey.
Not exactly Alcatraz, is it?
Get it.
What are we waiting for?
Come on, Susie.
Come on, walkies.
There you go.
The blue blooded girls.
Yes, sir.
Now, what about this one?
What about those two kids?
Could you sign the guest book, sir?
They've got a little sense into their heads, sir.
It just takes a little teenage psychology.
You want cheese on that?
Oh, forget it.
They're gone, little fools.
Damn, they saw the exit sign.
Forget it.
So you talked some teenage sense into them, did you?
Look, officer, they were scared to death.
Don't put this in the record.
I'll take the full responsibility.
Sam Howard?
Candy, it would be just dandy.
This my candy.
If you'd like to make a call, please, sir.
You still here?
No.
Well, of course I'm here.
Where should I be?
I saw your car drive off.
Who?
Oh, no.
If those kids have stolen my car, I...
Now, Mr. Rogers, you said you'd be responsible.
I hope you know what you're doing.
So do I.
That chick gets too hungry.
Boy.
Now.
Oh, I can't.
No, I can't.
I'll come back when they're done.
No, no, no.
Come on back.
That spaceship slipped by us.
I'm looking, I'm looking.
Shut up.
I'm late.
Hey, it is kind of late.
I wonder if they forgot about us.
Shut up.
But not too late for that date in town.
No, shut up.
I'm looking, I'm looking.
But it's kind of dull, though.
Blip, blip, blip, blip.
You're not funny.
Shut up.
I should snap on the infrared...
Yeah, we should snap your neck.
And get us court-martialed, you mean.
Okay.
Maybe they were killed in Vietnam.
Let's hope.
Snap on the infrared.
Snap on, snap off, the snaffler.
Take a peek at those kids in the line of business.
What else?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.